only when the well is dry will you know
the worth of the
water at the start notice a beautiful
pouring rain man a great running weather
right Austin my favorite this is going
to
suck right I really don't think I could
have picked a more [__] up way to
start a race how about you Austin a cold
muddy welcome to pwn Mountain
Austin is way better higher an hour to
make it over Pond Mountain ain't bad
dude dude is any place you'd rather be
right now than above the [__]
clouds on the 18 work dude it's like old
times ain't it bro when we get done we
should go like steal a 12pack of beer
from a grocery store and run away
cackling the grocery store's Barefoot
and trying to fight the manager hey
there's only one way to enjoy the great
outdoors with your best
friend so how many stars do you give the
spine of the Dragon yeah this shit's
[__] crazy beautiful man bro there we
go and the sun's coming out no longer
Happ does not disappoint does it
Austin maybe it
does what do you think dude this is my
new favorite part so far what do your
legs feel like right now like a little
tiny worm on a big hook I said your legs
not your
pecker
Austin what do you
think yeah I think we've passed the
Running part and reached the [__]
Ultra part I think so oh gut bomb kund
in Falls one mile dude this is a [__]
of a mile l in we're going to run
downhill relentlessly and then we get to
turn around and come
back come on baby last clim that's the
token of my appreciation for you doing
this dumb [__] with me I'm going to let
you name this stretch of godforsaken
mountain after we make it to the top
salt tabs coming baby what do you name
it I'm going to call it hill fky hill
Austin aens has named it the bunks a few
words on what you're seeing uh this is
God's country [__] ampala 17 miles
what time 4 hours 35 minutes we hit our
first and only aid station which is just
a goddamn Creek meletus Austin likes
Cheerios
oh that was close
safe bro man we made it last push shop
Pond Mountain hey let do it does it make
his P we're using walking sticks now
these are for when we fight mountain
lions we're almost there dog that's a
sight for S rise ain't it
[Music]
bro bro we did it we have thrown
ourselves against the mountain and we
did not break I got a good stick out of
it you look like a [__] Warrior
dog cuz you [__] are man here we go
again last one we [__] did it
Austin we're almost
there go
as time 7 hours 18 minutes 48 seconds
26.5 3 miles holy
[__] as iron sharpens iron Austin I love
you dog see that was the most fun I've
had in a long time I would give it a 10
out of a 10 bro the only way to finish a
trail race [__] [__] we them
guys ain't we dog we dogs hey boy bro oh
good
dogs [__] yeah face like freedom
[Music]